Imagine a world where you don't do any
more work, you don't spend any time in
people's DMs or begging people to jump on
a sales call, and you make more sales
simply by fixing one part of your business
strategy and structure, which
isn't even that difficult,
and you could literally do it today
or tomorrow and
start to see the results. Well, you can,
and that one thing is called a sales
page or a landing page. Now,
this video isn't scripted.
It's not planned, nothing.
I do this all day, every day in the
Discord. And quite frankly,
your sales page is shit.
How do I know?
Because the majority of sales pages
that I look at are shit.
Because you're doing what you do on social
media, which could be improved.
You're probably getting people's data
or moving them down the funnel to some
kind
of email marketing campaign,
which definitely could be improved.
But then you're sending people to your
sales page,
and you're sat there scratching
your head going, "Why
are people not buying my product?" Trust
me, they are the
right people for the product.
You've done everything right so far,
but you've sent
them to a shitty menu.
And I'm going to uncover the most common
problems that I
face, and I do apologize
if I get heated with this because it's
something that I'm
passionate about. First things first,
at the very top, have a promise, not
some ChatGPT title that you said,
"Give me a good title for a sales page."
And you're like, "Hey,
do you want to be the leanest you've ever
been, the best
you've ever felt?
Do you want to drop a jean size
and lose two inches off your
waist? Well,
I've got the thing for you." It looks
cheesy as shit.
Remember, on social media,
here's a great tip.
Never try and optimize for algorithms.
Optimize for human beings because that's
what you're trying to win over.
If you make an amazing YouTube video
optimized for humans and humans
enjoy it, guess what?
The algorithm gets really fucking excited
because that's what
the algorithm is. Happy humans,
happy algorithm.
So optimize your title for fucking normal
human beings.
Yes, I just said fuck,
but you might have noticed
that I don't even monetize this
channel. Just put a statement at the top.
Better yet, put a promise.
And put a good promise.
The best online training
or your money back.
The best golf swing you've ever had.
The driving range won't believe your
secret.
Whatever it is, promise at the top.
Don't make it cheesy.
Underneath that, a VSL,
a video sales letter, or a video
that just sells it.
And do not succumb to the "Hi,
my name's John.
I've been in the fitness industry for 15
years now, and I've been a personal
trainer. I've got lots of clients.
And the online program,
people asked for it for years, and
I just want"— We're 20 seconds into the
video.
I don't even know what it is
or what it's going to help me for.
I'm gone.
I don't care about you.
No one cares about you.
That's another social media strategy.
They just care about themselves.
And the only reason they're on their
landing page is to see whether or not
that you
can help them.
When you get onto my landing page for my
mentorship, the first thing
I'm talking about is what I created for
you, how it can help you and your
business. And there'll be a link for
that in the description, or 30 days
that you
can improve your business for free.
So good you'll probably steal it.
Everything is about you,
and the best I can help you,
like today in this landing
page video,
the better our relationship will be.
Because ultimately,
all you fucking care about is yourself.
And the only reason you're watching this
video isn't even that you like me that
much.
Some of you might be under the impression
you like me, but you actually just
like the fact that I turn up here on a
fucking daily and weekly basis making you
better at what you do.
That's really all it is,
and I'm okay with that.
And if we walk down the street,
and you give me a fist bump because I did
that,
that's fine. In that video,
don't over-edit it.
It's like a casual conversation.
It's like a consultation.
It's like a flipping first date.
You don't try too hard on a first date.
You get the perfect mix of effort,
not trying too hard.
Because if you turn up to a first date in
a fucking tuxedo, she's not texting you
back, bro.
There is a real simple formula for this
video.
What it is, why they need it,
what they get, why to trust you,
how to pay.
Put me on the spot, Declan.
Give me something to sell.
Not fitness,
because everyone seems to think I just run
a fitness program.
I help businesses.
But you can really put me on hot coals
here.
Give me a service or something
that I'm selling. Sell me the DJI mic.
What it is,
this is a receiver for the best audio
microphone that you can get.
The company is called DJI. This
is a three-and-a-half millimeter audio
jack
that goes into the camera.
And somewhere in this room
is the microphone.
The reason you need this
is because audio is a very,
very important part of
content.
And you can have the best-looking video in
the world, but if the audio's
shit, they're leaving. Considering
that you're communicating points across to
people that could impact their lives,
and also yours if they become clients,
audio
is not just a necessity,
it's a prerequisite.
When you purchase this,
not only do you get the receiver,
you get two microphones,
you get the audio jack,
and you also get a chargeable carry case
that you can take
and plug into USB-C,
and it charges all components at one
point.
Can you show me that case, please?
This means you don't have to worry about
not
having the right things on you at any
point, and you only have to charge one
device,
and all of your audio infrastructure
is taken care of.
If you look at the reviews online,
you can see just how popular this
is with the
thousands of people that use it.
Not to mention, if you don't find this
is the best
audio transmitter and receiver
that you've ever used,
there's a money-back
guarantee included in that. There
is a link just below this video where you
can
purchase.
I went through the exact same thing there.
What it is, why you need it, what you get,
why to believe you, how to buy.
Let's go again, Declan. This time,
not a physical product because that's
easy.
Give me a service. Just make it up.
Massage services.
[laughs] So I'm a masseuse. Okay.
There are only three types of
massage that you're going to need,
remedial, relaxing, and sports.
You will get a 30, 60,
or 90-minute massage,
depending on what you need
help with.
Whether it's to unwind after a stressful
day, whether it's to rub into
some of those knots that
are keeping you awake at night,
or whether it's just to
have an hour away from your phone,
face down on the bed,
not thinking about your
work life, and being able to unwind.
The reason that you need this is you
are too caught up with stressful devices,
your
kids, your partner.
You're plugged into the matrix all day,
and you need to start
setting aside time for yourself.
One to two hours a week where all
you have to do is disconnect from the
world, and let our team of qualified
masseuses make you feel better.
Your Medicare rebate will cover the
majority of the costs,
and we have one of the best practices in
the local area.
Now, I don't expect you to believe
that we are the best at what we do,
and quite frankly,
it would be unprofessional for me to say
that.
So what I'll do is this.
You book into any massage for any amount
of time at our
practice,
and the first massage isn't free.
We've got incredible masseuses,
they need to be paid.
But if you don't think this
is the best massage you've ever had,
you let me know
afterwards,
and we won't charge you for that massage.
So below this, there's a button.
You click on that,
and you can book in your first
massage with us, and hopefully,
it'll be the first of many.
I went through the same exact structure
there.
What it is, why you need it, what you get,
why to believe us.
Now, the why to believe us changed.
It was a money-back guarantee with the
massage because that's fine.
The reason to believe with this
was actually me saying to look at the
reviews, the
hard evidence. The reason
that we launched Nutonic so heavily on
Amazon to
begin with was because we wanted the
reviews.
We make less money through Amazon,
but we needed help with the reason to
believe.
So on your page, you've got your header,
you've got your promise, you've got your
VSL that can just be chilled.
It can be done on an iPhone at home.
We don't always want crazy production,
but we do want to make a bit of an effort.
And there are people that I work with
that get crippled with their VSL.
They go, "Oh,
I've been planning it for two weeks
and I've not done it yet." If you
cannot sit in front of camera like this
and tell me about your product and
service without having to script it,
then what the fuck are you doing with
yourself?
Because if you're a personal trainer who
wants to move online, if you're
a real estate agent
that wants to sell several million-dollar
houses, if you're
opening a masseuse parlor, or whether
or not you're selling electrical
microphones,
if you don't know your fucking product
inside out, then what the fuck
are you doing with yourself?
Declan could kick down the door in my
house, wake me
up at 3:00 in the morning,
and ask me any question about anything to
do with
social media, email marketing,
landing pages, sales process, and pricing,
and
all I need to do is rub my eyes
and I'm ready to go,
and I'll give you a fucking
TED Talk on it. Because these
are the two ultimatums here.
Either you know everything about the
product and service
and you're just being a
fucking pussy in front of the camera,
which is fine.
But trust me, put a fucking VSL,
sales video letter out there,
and every week record a new one.
And guess what?
It will get better week on week.
Or number two,
you're trying to sell something
that you don't know that much about.
And if that's the case,
you're a fucking fraud. So pick a side.
You're a fraud or you're scared. And
if you're scared, I don't care,
you still need
to make the fucking video.
Because having someone facing camera
representative of
the brand helps build trust.
The same way that the majority of you
when you go on
dating apps,
you find the person's Instagram so you can
see videos of that person
moving.
The biggest fucking red flag as a dude in
2025 is a
chick whose dating apps
and Instagram have no videos.
Because you know she's one of them chicks
that just looks hot in photos.
And the other reality is,
the majority of you need to see me
talk and speak to you
and help you for probably 10 to 15 videos
before you do
use the call to action
that I put in the description.
Because you need to gauge how well you can
know me.
If this was all Substack written content
or Twitter, it would take so much longer.
Cool. What goes underneath the video?
The text version of what we just said.
What it is, why they need it,
what they get, why to trust you,
how to buy.
Because some people just aren't interested
in watching the video.
They see the video, they go,
"Cool." They watch the first five seconds,
but they're
on the train.
And they're actually listening to their
favorite song that's a
banger,
so they're going to stop the video,
scroll down, they'd much rather read.
We are putting something there for people
that want the video.
that want to read.
They scroll down,
we give them the option to buy. Now,
two things.
One, show your fucking pricing.
I hate the idea that
people think they shouldn't have their
pricing there.
When I go to Porsche,
I want to know how much the car is.
When I buy a house,
I want to know how much the house is.
When I'm flying first or business class,
if these airlines didn't show me how much
it was, "Hey,
get on the phone with our business class
representatives and we can
talk about prices." Fuck you,
I'm going to another airline.
It's okay to be expensive.
You should be proud of your fucking
pricing.
If you're cheap, that's a good thing.
If you're expensive, that's even better.
Because people automatically associate
being expensive with being good.
It's called premium pricing.
There's a whole fucking cohort of it in
sales
psychology. Case in point,
if I wake up this morning
and my iPhone cable didn't
work, my alarm doesn't go off
and my phone's fucking dead, I'm fucked.
Now,
I want to go on the internet to get a
fucking replacement cable.
Am I going to get a cheap one?
There's one for $399, $499, $599, and
$20.
You best believe I'm getting the fucking
$20 cable. Why?
Because I don't want a repeat of what just
fucking happened today.
And if I get one of the cheap ones,
the statistical likeliness of
that happening
are much higher.
Three weeks down the line,
it happens again, and I go, "Fuck's
sake, buy cheap, buy twice."
And guess what?
The type of people
that want the cheap cable,
you don't want them as fucking
customers because they're just buying on
price.
The people that want it for $20 want
something that's reliable,
not going to let
them down,
it's going to do the fucking job,
and they don't care it costs more.
That sounds to me like a good customer.
Anyone that's told you to not show your
pricing is a fucking fraud,
and we all know
the fucking biggest snake oil salesman in
the whole realm of
fitness and wider are the people like,
"Hey, book in a free
discovery call so we can pressure you on
the phone." And the little questionnaires.
Fuck your questionnaires before you try
and sell to people.
Because this is classic sales 101.
"Hey,
fill out this questionnaire before we get
on the phone." And then what you do
is, "How much does this mean to you?
What are the implications if you
were to do this?
What are the implications
if you weren't to do this?" They use this
against you, so
when they drop the pricing and go,
"The business mentorship is 15 grand."
"Wow." You go, "Oh,
it's a little bit out my budget." "Well,
Sally, you said to
us that if you didn't accomplish your
business dreams for this year, that meant
that you and your husband would never get
to take the family away to Sri Lanka
business class. Is that right,
Sally?" "Yes." "Well,
don't you think it's the
right thing for you to spend the 15 grand
with us so that becomes a
reality?" "Oh, I suppose
when you..." Fucking snakes. Hate it.
Just show your damn pricing.
Because I'll-Ultimately,
if I'm going to go for dinner
somewhere and I want to have a look at the
menu, I go, "Hold on, there's no prices
on here. How can I budget?
How can I think about it?"
And some people go, "But the
pricing might deter people." It rarely
does.
You ever notice that Porsche, Ferrari,
McLaren, they don't do sales
because the people
that want those cars don't give a shit.
If your product is good
and you charge a lot for it,
showing your pricing should be
a good thing. And if they can't afford it,
they're going to go, "Fuck, this guy
must be good.
It's a shame I can't afford it." Let them
go because someone can, and
if you can market your business strong
enough, you can. Cool. Show your pricing.
Now, when I click
that join Pay Now button,
it shouldn't be a fucking apply form
because let's be real,
you're going to take everyone on.
It's not applying for a Soho House
membership for fuck's sake.
Apply for coaching. Fuck off, Derek.
You're desperate for clients as it is.
And when I see those forms, I'm like,
"Nah, I was ready to go,
brother." Book in a
call, a discovery call.
Your sales page should objection-handle
every
single question they have.
And as you go through more experience with
people,
you should be able to objection-handle all
of those things.
Oh, and better yet,
just offer them a month money-back
guarantee or a
two-month money-back guarantee.
"Oh,
I'd just really like to jump on a call
if that's possible." No, I'm busy.
I'm running a business.
Here's the money-back guarantee. Join.
If you don't love it, you get a refund.
Sales calls should not be in this process.
And the fact that you have Apply Now
or give me your name
and your email address
and your phone number on your fucking
sales page means
that your whole sales system
is fucked anyway because they should've
come from email marketing.
You should already have their contact
information before you send them to the
sales page.
You literally send people to a sale page
from an email marketing
campaign. Use a platform that
are designed for it.
Your Squarespaces look shit.
When you try and implement them into
AWeber or your
Mailchimp, they look shit.
For $49 a month, whatever it is,
you could use
Leadpages. And it's a bit expensive.
Do you know how much a fucking web
designer costs?
And they don't even know what they're
fucking doing half the time.
You end up getting a website
that looks nice but doesn't perform well.
Leadpages, I don't get paid by Leadpages,
gives you the analytics
of how many visitors,
how many people clicked on the fucking buy
button.
Better yet,
Leadpages lets you make A splits,
B splits, C splits so
you can see whether more text, less text,
more video, less video, longer page,
shorter page.
You can make 10 variations of the same
sales page, send everyone the
same fucking link,
then you can look at all the traffic
that lands on it and
learn what converts better
and what doesn't.
To hire someone to be in your sales
department would cost you thousands a
month.
To get a web designer, thousands.
To hire someone.
For $49,
Leadpages even gives you nice color
palettes because
dudes, you fuck the color scheme so much.
You never leave a man to make the bed,
ever.
You need a woman the majority of the time.
I'm not being sexist.
Women have just got this touch.
The pillows that go on the sofa,
the way the
curtains go over the room,
they're just amazing at it.
And when I see women's landing pages,
they look great.
And when I see dudes',
they make them using fucking red
and black.
Never use red in branding. Red
and black look shit.
Optimize your landing page to be easy to
read.
Don't put fucking pictures of you behind
the text.
Don't give people an opportunity to leave,
and don't give them too much to read.
Within a few minutes,
that person goes on a landing page to do
one thing, to
qualify themselves in or out. That's it.
And then over time, you make
that landing page better and better
and better using
the data and analytics in there.
Because your presumptions over people's
behaviors
are presumptions,
and until you have actual evidence to
stipulate this formula
works, you're just guessing.
Then over time,
you make your video better, you make
the page better, you keep making splits,
and soon, you send the same amount of
traffic that you did before
and way more fucking clients come out than
ever before.
This is only a small component of the
bigger picture.
A lot of other business mentorships tell
you to DM people, hang out on Facebook
groups, and do sales calls.
And let me tell you why.
You remember Joe Wicks, right?
Nice guy.
He did his fucking HIIT workouts for
everyone. Everyone.
Do you know why he sold HIIT workouts to
everyone?
Because everyone can fucking do a HIIT
workout.
When it comes to mass marketing a fitness
program, doing something that everyone
can do. Oh, you don't use the gym?
No problem. Oh,
you want to train from home?
No problem.
When it comes to making the most amount of
money, you want to give
something to someone
that even a fucking idiot can do.
Guess what?
DM-ing people,
hanging out on Facebook groups,
and doing sales calls, it's fucking
retard-proof, right? These mentorships
are giving you easy shit to
do because it doesn't require you to get
any better.
Where for me,
I need you to get good at understanding
sales pages, landing pages.
I need you to put out better content.
I need you to become a wordsmith in email
marketing, and I need you to deliver a
good fucking service.
If you can't do those four things
or you don't want to
do those four things, fuck off
and join the other shitty mentorships
because
ultimately,
I need you to get better at these things
because it's all I've done for
the last fucking 10 years.
So many of you are already doing the hours
and the
work. You're just not doing it very well,
and the fucking craziest thing is this.
The majority of you say to your clients,
"Don't guess your way through a workout.
Hire me and do it the right way." Yet you
guess yourself your way through your
landing pages, your website,
your email marketing,
your fucking social strategy.
You're hypocrites.
Follow those processes that I've done.
Make it look nice.
Choose the nice color palette.
Keep it fucking simple.
Don't make the text too small,
and get your video to do most of the work
for you.
Like I said at the very beginning of this
video, same amount of people are
visiting,
way more of them end up as clients.
More money, same amount of effort.
Just make a better fucking landing page.
Honestly, pissing me off